Synced by Anomix33
200 years ago Bijapur Sultanate was ruled by Raja Hari Man Singh .
In those days the fear of ghosts and spirits prevailed in the hearts of people .
The most feared demon of all was called Saamri .
One day Raja Man Singh was travelling with his daughter Rupali towards Bijapur
when his royal chariot broke down .
How long will it take ?
Only a little while , sire .
- Where has Rupali gone ? - She was just here .
Rupali , Rupali !
Princess !
She shouldn 't have left alone so late in the night . This is Saamri 's land !
Don 't just look at me ! Go and find her ! Go !
Saamri !
Cut him down ! Kill him !
Find him , find him ! That demon came this way .
Quickly !
This royal proclamation of Mughal King Hari Man Singh
states that Saamri using his satanic powers
has created terror in the state of Bijapur .
The accusation is that you unrobed young married women
and violated their honor .
You are accused that to slake your satanic thirst
you mercilessly killed young and innocent children
and sucked their blood .
You have fallen so low from the human level
that even Satan would shun you .
To strengthen your evil powers you opened graves
took out corpses
and
and ate them .
O , King , destroy this creature now !
No ! Entomb him in the wall .
King ...
I believe that this monster should be purged in pure fire
and thus be turned forever into ashes .
No , holy man .
This demon 's head will be separated from his body .
The body will be buried in the ruins behind this temple .
And his head
will remain under guard in my palace , far from here .
That way , his head and his body will never be joined together .
I beg you , my lord , guard the head with this holy trident of Shiva .
Thus will all this demon 's powers be rendered ineffective .
' The old temple . '
Hari Man Singh
I curse you !
As long as my head and body remain apart
all your female heirs will die horribly ..
... as soon as they give birth to their first child !
And the day my head and body are joined again
will be the end of your dynasty !
And so Hari Man Singh cut off the head of that demon
and kept it apart from the body .
The body was buried in the ruins behind Shankar 's Palighat temple .
The demon 's head was put in a trunk fastened with chains .
Raja Hari Singh secured that trunk in the dungeon of his palace .
God Shiva 's holy trident was put on top of the trunk .
A wall was built across the door of the dungeon
and the severed head was hidden from the eyes of the world .
A painting of Hari Man Singh was hung on the door .
And so the stories of Saamri 's evil faded
into the darkness of the dungeon .
The river of time carried off the main players .
The faces of Sher Khan , Rajguru Balbir Singh and all the rest
became lost in the mists of time .
The flame of Hari Singh 's life was extinguished .
After him the reins of the state fell to Prithipal Singh
and then in the course of time , Raja Ajit Singh .
After him , Thakur Ranbhir Singh sat on the throne .
The dusts of time settled over the ancient palace
and it became forgotten about .
The pulse of life left the palace area and moved to the city .
This is the last remaining heir of Hari Man Singh - Ranbir Singh .
A grand and important man , even today .
But the fear of Saamri still prevails in his heart and mind .
Sir , these papers need your signature .
Give me a pen .
Have you sent the payment to Gawahar Saw Mills ?
Brother , dear .
Dayawanti , has Suman left for college ?
Really papa , what kind of talk is that ?
Does your daughter ever go to college without meeting you ?
And that is why I have been rushing home .
I knew my little doll would be waiting for me .
You call me your little doll ! But see how tall I 've grown !
I reach your shoulders .
Brother , the child has grown up .
Grown up !
Papa what 's the matter ? What are you thinking ?
Nothing , my dear .
I was just thinking ... aren 't you getting late for college ?
OK , papa . Bye Papa .
Bye , auntie .
I know the sorrow in your heart .
If only I could share it .
In this world , every father prays for his children to grow up .
But I ...
I am an unlucky father who wishes that ..
.. there shouldn 't be any marriage ceremony in this house .
Because of that accursed palace !
So finally you come , your lordship !
And I 've only been waiting an hour .
What are you staring at ?
Just one close up .
You 're getting obsessed about your close-ups !
Naughty boy ! Let me go ...
I don 't blame you .
I wouldn 't mind some of that myself .
Hey , dude ! You 're cruising for a bruising .
But why are you still just taking pics ?
What 's your problem ?
Her father .
Doesn 't he know about you two ?
Not yet .
So you 're still only dreaming ?
Get a move on , chum .
Or you 'll wake up and find yourself alone in bed .
Here 's the dream girl .
How 's Sapna ?
What are you gossiping about ?
He was telling me about his bed .
Bed ? I don 't get it ...
I 'll explain later .
Hey Anand , coming to the club this evening ?
Yes Anand , and bring Sapna .
- I don 't know ... - Why not ?
I 'll have a show of my own to watch .
I am already 45 minutes late .
The first question will be :
Where 've you been ?
What were you doing ? Who with ?
I 'm young and lonely .
You don 't know how lost I am .
Thousands fawn on me but even so I 'm lonely .
Yes me , yes me .
The moon and stars in my eyes
who knows who they call today ?
Somebody please read their signs
and come and bring me joy and more .
Become my ... oh , become my lover , lover .
The business of the heart , only the heart understands .
What can you or I do about it ?
What is a dream and what is the truth ? Who will know that here ?
Live for the moment , oh live for the moment , lover .
Papa , I 'm back .
Sorry I 'm late again .
I met my old girlfriend Nikki and she insisted I go back with her .
And her parents asked me to stay for a while .
They insisted that I have dinner with them .
Papa , have you eaten ?
Who is this boy ?
It 's Sanjay , papa .
He 's a really nice boy .
- If you met him ... - You 'll not see him again .
Please meet him just once . He 's from a respectable family .
Please meet him once .
Ranbir Singh 's family blood has not become so thin
that it can flow away in the gutters .
I knew it , Suman ...
I knew that your father 's money would be a wall between us .
Even so Sanjay , why won 't you meet Papa one day ?
I 'm sure if he met you , all these problems would be solved .
No , Suman .
He 'd just reject me because I 'm poor .
So now I see how my own blood wants to shame me .
And how this man is now my mortal enemy .
You fool ...
If you burn palace lamps in a hovel
you won 't get light , you 'll burn the hovel down .
But if there 's a fire , the must be some light .
Not for long .
In a poor man 's life , even a brief light is worth much .
Today 's love is not love , it 's just the fever of youth .
How much ?
How much money do you want , to leave my daughter alone ?
Sorry , sir
true love can 't be bought and sold .
You blacken our good family name
and now you argue with me !
Teach him respect !
Let him go , papa . Please !
Stay off my friend !
Come you bastard dogs , where are you running off to ?
We showed ' em .
I don 't understand .
If Suman wants you , what 's his problem ?
The problem 's always been there , and it always will be .
I cannot ignore the heritage of this family .
But what about your daughter 's wishes ?
This child 's tears are not something that I want
but that vagabond will take her away from me forever .
But I won 't let that happen .
I won 't even let his shadow fall on her again .
Why can 't you make this girl understand , Dayawanti .
Make her understand , or I dread the consequences .
Who ... Who are you ?
I am asking you , who are you
that has for centuries cast a shadow of death on this family ?
How much more blood must flow ? How many more will you kill ?
How many more lives ?
You can 't kill her . You can 't ever take my child away from me .
Papa what happened ?
Nothing , just go back to your room .
After today you will never meet Sanjay again .
And if he tries to see you , I will have him killed .
Don 't just stand there , get out of here .
Those gone days I remember . Those stolen moments I recall .
The ones I spent with you , warm in your embrace .
That smile of yours , your blushes , the time of December , the wet cold .
What happened to those days , where did they all go ?
Only the memories remain .
Those talks I remember , the nights I remember .
Spent with you , holding you close .
Wrapping yourself around me , lowering your eyelids .
Still in my heart remains the softness of your lips .
Now you 've started a fire .
I wonder where you 've gone . Only the memories remain .
Suman , I love you .
Driver , let 's go .
Something is happening to me ...
I don 't want to die ... !
Save me ! Please , save me ... !
Come , Suman .
I return your family 's honor to you , sir .
If I wanted I could have made your lamp the light of my hut ...
But I feared that this flame might have burnt down your palace .
I 'm going .
Wait !
You may as well take this gun
and shoot both her and me .
What ?
I am not upset about my defeat , I am upset at your victory .
Because you will run from her once you know the truth .
The truth ? What truth , papa ?
It 's ... It 's a secret .
What kind of secret ?
One I can 't reveal .
But you must reveal it .
No , I can 't tell you ! I can 't tell you ...
This secret is a curse that has cast the shadow of death on our family .
What kind of curse is it , to become a wall between our love ?
You have to reveal it Papa , my happiness depends on it .
Please tell us .
All right ...
Alright , if you really want to know ...
So be it .
Do you see that palace ?
That building is such a cursed stain on our family
that we could not wash it away
even with our own blood .
Every mother , every woman connected with this building
on the birth of her first baby becomes the immediate prey of death .
Papa , this is just a superstition .
It is not a superstition , it 's the truth .
But , sir ...
Can you really believe such things , in this day and age ?
Look ...
I don 't believe in things that people tell me .
But I 've seen this with my own eyes !
The day Suman was born
this curse ... took away her mother Bharti from us .
Something 's happening to me ! - Are you okay ?
Something is happening to me ! I don 't want to die ... !
What 's wrong ?
I don 't know , sir ...
- I can 't understand ... - What 's happened to Bharti ?
Go and look !
What 's wrong ?
If , after knowing all this , you don 't leave Suman alone
then I know that you don 't love her but are her mortal enemy .
So you walked out on her ? You loser .
What 'll she think of you now ?
You don 't understand Anand . I really do love Suman .
I can 't live without her . Do you hear me ? I can 't live without her .
- But if you 'd heard that story ... - It 's nonsense ...
Just a made up story .
Suman ... What are you doing here ?
Sanjay ...
We must go to Bijapur .
Yes , to the old temple that 's the root of all our problems .
No , Suman ...
It 's better that you forget all about me .
For the sake of my love , I 'm not prepared to sacrifice your life .
While I 'm alive , nothing will happen to Suman .
I am here for you .
And if it comes to it , my life is yours .
You 'll come with us ?
Not only me , but Sapna as well .
She 'll be company for Suman .
- Does your father know ... ? - No ...
I didn 't tell him ...
But I left a letter for him .
Brother ... !
Terrible news ...
- Suman is not in her room ! - What ... ?
But I found this letter there .
Father , I cannot live without Sanjay .
If this family curse is the barrier to our love
then we will return only after destroying it .
We are going to Bijapur .
To the old palace .
Suman .
I still say you should go back , Anand . This is our problem .
Why risk your life for us ?
You 're asking for a thump , my old mate .
A friend is one who gives his own life if need be .
If there 's a shadow on our family , why should we allow it to fall on you ?
It 's no shadow ...
It 's in your father 's mind , now it 's got into your head too .
Hey , why did you stop the car ?
What is it ?
The tyre is punctured .
See mate , you need me after all !
If we start getting troubles so soon ..
... we might reach Bijapur in the next life !
Why did this problem have to arise now ?
We 're dead .
Why 's that ?
I forgot the jack .
I don 't believe it !
Don 't worry my king ! What do you think I 'm here for ?
You just deal with the tire , and I 'll be the jack .
Ranbir Singh ! Now it 's your daughter 's time !
She will suffer the same fate as your wife .
No ! You can 't do that ... !
Dayawanti !
Take it away .
I 'm afraid he 's had a heart attack .
He needs a lot of rest .
In his condition he can 't make the long trip to Bijapur .
This temple looks pretty old .
Indeed .
I don 't feel like driving any more . Why don 't we stay here ?
Alright , Suman ?
Yes Sanjay , I agree with Anand .
Besides , we 're all dead tired .
Looks like there 's no priest staying at this temple .
How would he , Anand ?
Is it a joke to climb up and down 200 steps every day ?
It may be for you , but not for me .
Hail to the Lord !
Look , Anand , this is odd .
What ?
This Shiva has no trident in his hand .
Right !
Who would look after this temple if there 's no priest here ?
Right mate , now we 've met God , lets go and meet the saint .
What saint ?
Saint Food ! I 'm starving .
Mice are doing a dance in my stomach .
Suman ... ! What are you doing here ?
Why don 't you speak ? What happened ?
It was ...
I saw ...
What did you see ?
I saw a corpse , Sanjay ...
With no head ... !
It was coming at me .
Sanjay it wanted to kill me .
You 're talking crazy .
Sanjay ... I heard strange noises .
Strange noises .
A walking corpse , and without a head too !
There 's nothing here .
You 're tired and had a bad dream .
That man seems to be belonging to this place ... .
He must know the old palace .
- I 'll be right back . - I 'm coming . - Come back soon .
Excuse me ...
Do you know the way to Bijapur ?
The palace at Bijapur . Thakur Man Singh 's palace .
Do you know the way , sir ?
What happened ?
Strange man .
He was waving that axe like he wanted to cut my throat !
Looks deserted to me .
There must be a watchman about .
- You two stay here . - OK .
We 'll be back .
Watchman ! Gardener !
Anyone here ?
I just saw a light over there .
- Where ? - Over there .
Can 't see anyone .
Let 's go .
What is it ?
There 's someone by the car .
Anand , ask her who she is .
Who are you ?
Why don 't you answer ?
She is dumb .
My mother ... Mangli .
So who are you ? Where is the watchman ?
I am Durjan , the watchman of this place .
Who are you ?
We 're from Bombay .
She 's Suman , daughter of Ranbir Singh .
We are honored .
After many years , someone from the family has returned .
Come , come inside .
This is the palace of your grandfather , Raja Pratap Singh .
This is your grandfather 's picture , Raja Pratap Singh .
And this is your great grandfather 's picture , Raja Ajit Singh ...
This is all very fascinating ...
But I really need sleep .
I 'm sleepy too .
And here is Hari Man Singh , your grandfather 's , grandfather .
What 's up ?
I feel drawn towards that painting ...
Like he 's trying to tell me something .
Really ?
Come .
Come on , Suman .
Have a good night ?
Great fun .
Lying on the royal bed I dreamt royal dreams all night long .
Me king of kings and Sapna my queen of beauty .
Suman ! What is it ?
You ! Why are you here ?
Food !
It must be cooked .
Oven must be lit .
Durjan called me , so I came .
What 's wrong , boss ?
Did you ask that man to come ?
Why ?
Without wood how will we cook ?
And only Sangha brings wood for the village .
Don 't ask him here again , understand ?
Let 's go .
6 ... 7 ... 8 ...
What a beautiful lake ! What a lovely place !
And in such a place
instead of talking love , the fool is working out !
Do you have to do that ?
Take a break .
Now stop it or I 'm going .
I 'm coming , miss .
So , what 's up ?
Nothing at all .
If you come any closer
I might melt like candle wax .
Until only the wick is left .
You just don 't understand .
These days it 's really important to keep the body fit .
Always thinking of your body , never of me !
If I think about you , the Indian population might explode .
What kind of talk 's that ? !
- I 'm off . - Where ?
To Hell .
This is a jungle , not hell , some bear will eat you .
Big deal .
More fun than watching you do press-ups .
OK , go then , go on ...
Just remember to call if you need me .
Synced by Anomix33
Let me go !
Sons of mice ! How many men were they ?
I am asking you - how many were they ?
Just one , sire .
Him , one man ! And six of you !
Yet you return without the girl !
Shame on you ! Sons of pigs ... !
So tell me , how much reward
has the Sardar put on my head ?
15,000 rupees ... ! 15,000 !
Now you 've made my name mud !
But punishment will come ... It will certainly come .
People are killed by bullets .
But I am going to kill you by making you eat bullets !
Give me a hand . You fell down yourself .
Come on , get up .
I am going to kill you by feeding you bullets .
What will I do ? Feed you bullets !
But these are laxative pills .
Last year , we gave two pills to twelve people each .
They are still wandering the jungle with their pots !
Clever , very clever .
That is all very well sir , but what will come of Murtar Singh ?
Murtar Singh ?
You have grown old , but still you sway .
A lot of strength in your legs , a lot of strength in the legs .
Give me Murtar 's Singh 's legs ! Bring me his legs !
Sardar why are you having studs put in your shoes ?
To squash Machar Singh .
He cut off my arms .
My name is Murtar Singh .
He has woken the flame of revenge in me .
I will beat him with my studded shoes .
Machar ! Give me those hands !
Your hands !
Sardar , I have been robbed , destroyed .
What 's wrong , Basanti ?
How can I tell you ? I 'm too ashamed to tell you .
If you 're too ashamed to tell me , I won 't be able to do justice .
That scoundrel , he dishonoured me .
You mean rape !
And this is the second time .
Who was it this time ?
Who else in this village except that rogue Machar ?
Stung by Machar a second time !
Sardar if he does it again , we 'll have a malaria epidemic !
There 'll be no epidemic .
We 'll spray DDT .
We will kill Machar with insecticide .
Increase the reward by one rupee !
Shall I lay the table ?
Please .
Durjan ... What do you know about this palace ?
It 's a mysterious place , sire .
I 've heard stories about it from my father and grandfather .
In the time of Hari Man Singh there was a dreadful incident
which still casts a shadow over this palace .
The tribals believe ...
there 's a link between this palace and the ancient temple of Palighat .
You ... ?
Here ... ?
Put it down and go .
Those town folk were asking questions about the palace .
What do you think they 're looking for ?
I know everything .
Everything ... !
They have come to find the treasure that 's buried here somewhere .
Whenever I mention the treasure , your mother goes crazy .
My mother knows a lot about this old palace .
But she can 't tell us , because she is dumb .
But I have told you many times , there 's treasure in this palace , there is .
What makes you so certain there 's anything here ?
If there was no treasure
why would they come to this lonely , desolate place ?
Let 's take a photo of you two .
It 's not a passport type photo . Give a romantic pose .
Like this ?
I 'm too embarrassed to look in the camera .
Mate , have you hooked one yet ?
The fish here are too clever , they don 't want to bite .
What 's she saying ?
I think she 's saying , she 'll catch the fish for you .
- How 'll she do that ? - She 's gone .
Now you 're for it .
Let 's go .
We don 't need these fish , we can go to the market .
- " I am hungry , bring me food , food , FOOD ... " - Shut up !
Is this a fish or a crocodile ?
Suman has brought this crocodile from the market
to put you off going fishing for yourself !
Anand , the female race are always suspicious .
Rightly so .
Suman come down , the food is getting cold .
Take those photos later .
Coming ... !
That was the last photo .
What 's wrong ?
The picture ...
What 's wrong with it ?
Nothing at all .
Suman , the food 's getting cold .
What is it ?
That painting ...
I saw a horrible face .
His head was cut off and blood dripping from his neck .
You 're amazing , Suman !
In the temple you saw a body with no head .
And here you see a head with no body .
A pretty good tale !
Don 't you believe me ?
Come on , let 's go and eat .
Who 's sitting on this donkey ?
It 's not a donkey , it 's a race horse .
There 's a 15,000 rupee reward on his head .
And you 'll catch him ?
Of course .
After coming all this way , might as well make some dough .
Watch , in two days I will grab this ass from his donkey .
On the river bank , Nandlal teases me .
It 's Basanti ... !
Oh , God !
The pot is broken ! Broken !
Let me go . I beg you , let me go .
Do you beg of me , or wink at me ?
I won 't do anything to you today . I won 't even touch you .
See , I have let you go .
But I will watch you dance .
Dance ? I don 't know how to dance .
Listen doll , don 't try to be clever with me . Come on , dance !
What is this ? Is this an arm or an elephant 's trunk ?
Let me breathe !
I can breathe ! I can breathe now !
Come with me . - Where ?
I 'm taking you to Sardar , Machar Singh .
I will turn you in and get the 15,000 reward .
But what will I get ?
A rope around your neck .
Bring the bastard here .
I have come of my own free will ...
Machar Singh !
- Yes , cripple ... ? - You 've committed terrible crimes .
But some fun ones too ! Isn 't that true , Basanti ?
You abandoned the young and nubile village girls .
Broke their hearts .
Turned your face from them .
And formed a relationship with 70 year old Basanti !
Whether Basanti is 70 or 16
in the country where Ganges flows she 'll always be moist .
You 're about to be hung , so stop beating about the bush .
I am beating about the bush , but I 'm not beating anything else , am I ?
I will beat you so much that your love engine will shut down .
Take him off to the gallows now !
Who are you to force me up the gallows ?
I 'll go by myself .
There 's no gallows in the world strong enough to hang me !
Stop , baldie !
I was having a conversation , how did you get in the middle ?
Wait for me , Basanti !
He 's run away !
And so should you .
When I catch him again
I 'll stamp on both your bodies with my studded shoes .
Who are you ? Think you 're Sunny Deol ?
I was really angry with that man . I was going to wring his neck .
Who are you , my saviour ?
Please remove your hood . Show me your face .
You ! You arrested me and now you ...
And now I freed you .
Why ?
It 's a business , mate .
What kind of business ? Let me hear it as well .
Look , I capture you and get the reward
free you , capture you again , get another reward and so on .
And what about my share of this reward ?
25 per cent is my best offer .
And 75 percent to you ?
Shall I take you to Sardar ?
Who 'll save you then ?
You drive a hard bargain .
Agree or not ?
75 percent ... That seems very fair .
I mean , 25 percent . Alright . I agree , I agree ...
Now you 're being sensible . Here 's your share .
What happened ?
Open the door .
That demon wants to kill me ... ! Get me away from here ... !
No , Suman . No .
We came to Bijapur to prove something .
There is no evil curse .
It 's just a trick to scare us off .
Who 's responsible for this ?
Answer me .
Answer me , Durjan !
You can 't deny what your own eyes see , master .
This is not a trick by a human but a manifestation of a demon .
If you really want to understand this
you must ask the villagers to help .
Bijli , I need to talk to you ... But you must put some clothes on .
I understand Hindi , these ARE my clothes .
Come and get me .
Will you stay with me ? I want to keep you .
Keep ... ? But first you ...
Is this what you came all the way from Bombay for ?
It 's very important that I talk with Bijli .
At least now I know what 's important to you .
Are you coming with me or staying with this jungle slut ?
Suman , I told you , it 's important that I talk to Bijli .
Then she 's obviously much more important to you
than me !
Let 's go , Bijli .
Enough Bijli ... I can 't drink any more .
I was already drunk from your lovely eyes .
You have only drunk from my eyes ...
When your lips are pressed against my lips
then your body will really catch fire .
I remember those bygone days .
Those stolen moments
spent with you , hugged against my body .
In your arms I cuddled , you wrapped up in my hair .
Time has taken all but memories . Why have the dreams shattered ?
That past life , our happiness , romantic places , time of desires .
Our tormented hearts , the pounding heart beats .
The songs we hummed .
They are lost , gone with the wind . Why have the dreams shattered ?
Come along .
Stop right there !
If you don 't , then I swear by Kali this knife will go through you .
Don 't , it 's my brother .
How do you dare touch the hand of Raka 's sister ?
Bijli ? Who is this boy ?
This is Sanjay .
He wants to ask us about the palace and old temple .
Stay away from that palace and the old temple
or be lost forever in the darkness of death .
Death 's darkness can 't stop me from reaching my goal .
What goal ?
Your goal means the destruction of our village and our tribe .
200 years ago an abomination was buried in that ground .
You want to raise it ! To destroy it !
No ...
City boy ...
Go back to your city and never come here again .
Or I swear by the goddess Kali , I will slit your throat .
You don 't scare me .
But keep your knife sharp
it might be handy for cutting vegetables .
Oh Suman , did you really think that I had left you for that wild girl ?
Why don 't you understand ?
It was to find out the secrets of the palace .
It was just a show for the tribals .
Honestly ?
I swear ...
Now do I get a smile ?
Just a little one ... ? Just for me ... ?
I was getting some enjoyment , now even that has gone .
You dried up old fruit , are you giving a massage or polishing me ?
- Am I some shoe ? - No .
I am Machar Singh , my back is built like a brick wall .
So give me a hard slap .
A clap , was it a clap ? No , it was a gunshot . I 'm off !
You guys got afraid for nothing . He 's one of ours .
Hey friend ! What news ?
The news is good . The reward 's been doubled .
Really ?
But this time you won 't be hung .
What will they do ?
Your punishment 's been changed .
To what ?
This time you will be put in a live bear 's cage .
That 's great news , I haven 't seen a live bear for ages .
A live bear !
I 'll be torn to shreds in that cage .
You 'd better come up with a good plan .
Why , are you scared ?
It won 't be a real bear .
Inside the bear skin will be your very good friend .
You 're a true magician , just like a sheep in wolf 's clothing .
And I will stand in front of you , puff out my chest and say ...
Murtar Singh , you are a dead man , for sure .
Surrounding me with spears .
Putting me in the bear cage , you 're trying to kill me .
Hey Blackie , you open your ears and listen to me too .
You think you 're safe inside that cage .
But as soon as you come out , I 'll make kebabs of you
and sell them at the train station .
Idiot , it 's Anand .
So , you 're Anand .
And this is a real bear .
I 'm real too .
I couldn 't find a bear skin .
Couldn 't find a skin ?
Sardar , he 's run off again .
You 'd better run off too !
Injustice has been done to me .
Machar Singh has run away .
I belong neither there nor here .
Don 't worry .
I will do Emperor Jehangir type of justice .
Even Jehangir will come to seek my forgiveness .
I will marry you .
Marriage ? With you ?
- Both your hands have been cut off . - So ?
It 's only the hands .
Who needs hands to marry ?
After marriage , we will fly to London for the honeymoon ...
Air India .
I 'll get new hands made there .
That 's very funny !
My teeth are false too , I will get new ones made there .
And one more thing , I 'm bald , so I 'll get a new wig there too .
Who 's there ?
Who is it ?
I 'll kill you ...
Kill you ! ... KILL YOU !
Let me go ! I 'll kill him !
Who will you kill ?
That painting .
I keep telling you , there 's nothing in that painting .
Have you gone mad ?
Come with me .
Oh my foot .
Come on , Anand .
Have you gone nuts like Suman ?
How can a painting bleed ?
You saw the blood on Suman 's hand ?
She had no cuts .
- Some sort of trick . - And that crack behind the picture ?
Another trick ?
A crack ?
I saw it with my own eyes .
There 's an opening behind the painting .
And it must lead to somewhere or something .
You check that side ... and I 'll look over here .
There 's nothing here .
Find anything ?
No .
A strange place .
No-one 's been here for years .
Over there .
A trident ?
Anand ... What could be in that box ?
Open it .
I told you there was treasure here .
It 's a ... severed head !
Maybe some brave soldier 's .
The king must have kept it securely in memoriam .
Tomorrow we 'll get Durjan to have this area bricked up again .
They 'll be back to take the treasure .
- Let 's take it now . - Not yet .
Why ?
Tonight
when they 're asleep I will get my cart
and wait behind the back door of the palace .
And you can bring the treasure there .
Right ... Right ...
Let 's go and wait for the lights to go out .
Do it gently ! It hurts .
It 's a sprain .
She 'll have to stay in bed for at least 2-3 days .
No walking or moving at all .
Look here .
Now Suman will be able to get around .
I found this wheelchair downstairs .
It 's getting late . We should try to get some rest .
No ! No , Sangha . No !
Stop !
No ...
Bastard ... ! Stop !
You 've killed my mother ! I won 't let you live ... !
I won 't let you open the box , I won 't let you have the treasure !
Master ... ! It 's a calamity ! A calamity , master ... ! Master !
What 's up , Durjan ?
Why are you shouting so much ?
Master , you must stop Sangha !
He has taken the head and run off towards the old temple .
Stop him master , come quickly .
But , Durjan , why did Sangha take the head to the temple ?
If that demon Saamri 's head was found in this palace
then his body must have been buried near the old temple .
If the head and body are joined then the demon will come alive again .
Master , go and stop Sangha . Go !
Faster ! Faster !
Stop , Sangha !
Where 's she gone ?
Durjan , where is Sapna ?
She was here .
What 's that noise ?
Don 't be afraid .
I 'll be right back .
But first I 'd better go and close the main palace gates .
Anand , let 's check the ruins .
Anand - coffin .
What happened ?
Yes I am Anand , what happened ?
- Anand , he was here ... - Who was here ?
- Anand he wants to kill me . - Who wants to kill you ?
What happened here ? Where 's Sapna ?
Sapna 's , gone . I don 't know where she is .
What happened ?
Stop Sapna !
Don 't take another step .
Don 't go near the demon , Sapna !
Saamri !
I 'm not afraid of dying !
Show yourself , damn you !
You won 't get away from me !
Sapna ... What 's going on , Sapna ?
What is it ? What 's wrong ?
You seem terrified ...
I 've just had a terrible dream ! A dreadful nightmare ...
Dayawanti , Suman 's life is in danger !
I can 't stay here .
I must go to Bijapur , today .
Now you 've woken the demon from his sleep of centuries .
There will be such a flood of death , that all be washed away in it .
And you people are responsible for it .
I swear by Goddess Bhadarkali , there 's only one way to escape this fate .
A blood sacrifice of you two to Bhadarkali .
Hail Bhadarkali !
The one that I was dying for , he has to die today .
The faithless in love we must settle their account today .
The faithless in love , we must settle their account today .
My love your life it soon will end .
Death is going to fulfill its revenge today .
The world changed with the fire of rage . The moth is still alive .
It has to get burnt while swaying .
This game is from births .
There are many dangers in the path of love . Be careful .
Understand the gestures and listen to me . Win or lose .
Run away , mister !
Let him go .
I swear by Bhadarkali , Raka will cut this girl into pieces .
With these hands I will sacrifice her blood to the goddess .
If you want to save her , then you must fight me .
Listen ! I want that city dog , dead or alive .
Let 's search the jungle . Come on !
Let 's not stay here anymore .
Let 's get out of here now . Come on , let 's go .
Yes , Suman but we have to find Anand first .
He must be at the temple looking for the demon .
Let 's go .
Where is your friend ? Where have you hidden him ?
Where is my sister 's killer ? Speak !
Let me go . I don 't know .
Speak bastard , or I will skin you alive .
I said I don 't know .
Now let me go , I have a mission to kill .
And so do I , as you 'll find out .
Let go of me .
I said , let me go . I said , LET ME GO !
Hail Bhadarkali !
Before you can get to them , you have to get past me !
Sanjay , get Suman out of here . I 'll deal with this .
Have you gone mad , Anand ? I can 't leave you here .
Don 't argue Sanjay !
This demon feeds off the blood of Suman 's family .
He 'll kill her .
No ! I can 't leave you to face this alone .
We live together and die together .
Go ! Go ! Suman 's life is at stake !
Take her and get out of here !
Go ! Go !
Get Suman out of here !
A friend is someone who gives his own life if need be .
Papa , look what 's happened .
Anand sacrificed his life to save us .
And the demon killed Sapna too .
No man has the power to combat this demon .
Only one mighty power can destroy him and that is Lord Shiva .
Let 's go and beg for our lives from him .
Shiv Shankar . Shiv Shankar , simple one .
You are the one who gives life to all . You are the mighty preserver .
In the middle of the river , you are the bank .
Your strength created the two worlds .
Oh creator of all , Shiv Shankar , Shambo , Bholenath .
You are the giver , you are the mother and father of all .
Your glory shines .
Strong one , the strength of all , your devotee calls you .
Open your eyes Lord , give us your divine protection .
This is an old temple of yours , we have surrounded it .
Where have you lost your trident ?
How can you have lost it in front of the demon ?
Speak mighty one , speak God , speak .
Suman , we need that trident .
- Trident ? - Yes , God Shankar 's trident .
We can kill this monster with it .
And I 've seen it in the palace .
Come .
It was here !
Suman , that trident was here !
Look there .
Suman , this coffin was in the old temple .
The old temple ?
Yes , but how did it get here ?
That trident must be here .
Somewhere in this palace .
Don 't look in his eyes , Suman !
Suman ! Don 't look in his eyes ! Suman , no !
What 's that noise ?
We 'll see .
But the demon ... ?
While God Shiva 's trident is on it , the demon can 't leave the coffin .
Let 's go .
Burn it ! Turn this palace into ashes !
Let the demon burn together with this evil palace !
People of Bijapur , stop right there !
You can 't burn down this palace !
Give me ... just half an hour 's grace .
And within that half hour , in front of this palace
I myself will burn that demon to ashes in front of your eyes .
And if you can 't subdue the demon within that time , then what ?
Then go ahead and burn it down .
Come villagers ...
Come and burn this demon in the village square !
Open it .
Open it !
Start the fire !
Let this demon burn .
Burn him !
Son , I am proud of you .
You have destroyed the curse that has haunted our family
for 200 years !
God bless you . God bless you .
Synced by Anomix33